Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Leo Deaner collection 1902-2006 IBT0022
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Teamster Election Files, 1991-1996; Series 8; 12 Linear Feet
  - 1998 Rerun Election, 1987-1999; Series 8 Subseries 3; 1.5 Linear Feet
    - Hoffa Press Conference- November, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 22)
    - EO- Teamster Magazine- Hoffa, 1998 June; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 23)
    - Hoffa Finances, 1997-1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 24)
    - EO- Hoffa Cleared, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 25)
    - Edelstein- Hoffa Cleared, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 26)
    - Hoffa Cleared- Appeals Master, 1998 May 15; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 27)
    - Esquire Magazine, 1998 March; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 28)
    - NY Times Magazine, 1998 February 8; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 29)
    - Hoffa Arbitrations, 1987 June 9; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 30)
    - Hoffa Arbitrations, 1993 February 19; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 31)
    - Hoffa Arbitrations, 1993 April 10; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 32)
    - Hoffa Slate- Nominations, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 33)
    - DeSanti Leaflets, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 34)
    - DeSanti Campaign, 1996-1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 35)
    - DeSanti Leaflets, 1997; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 36)
    - Flyers Sent to the Network, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 37)
    - Flyers Sent to Network, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 38)
    - Anti-Ken Hall Leaflets, 1998; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 39)
    - Flyers Sent to Hoffa Slate, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 40)
    - Metz Leaflets, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 41)
    - Padellaro Leaflets, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 42)
    - Hoffa- East Region Leaflets, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 43)
    - Hoffa Slate National Flyer, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 3 (Box 90, Folder 44)
  - 2001 Election, Series 8 Subseries 4; 1.5 Linear Feet
    - Original Box List for 2001 Election, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Hoffa Certified, 2001 December; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Media- Hoffa Victory, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - Colon Shot, 2001 November 19; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Hoffa Observers, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - $100,000 Club, 2001 October 15; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - September 2001 Hoffa Slate Meeting, 2001 September; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Leebove, 2001 August 7; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Hoffa Mailings- Local Leaders Buy-In, 2001 August-September; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Election Administrator (EA)- Brentwood Mail, 2001 September-October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 10)
    - Hoffa Victory Party, 2001 November 17; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 11)
    - TDU- Carey Innocent, 2001 October 12; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - TDU- 12 Ways to Measure Hoffa, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Teamster Magazine, 2001 August-October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 14)
    - Hoffa Voting Guide, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 15)
    - Hoffa Homepage, 2001 July 2; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 16)
    - EA- Notice Postings, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 17)
    - IBT- Get Out The Vote, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 18)
    - The Debate, 2001 August-October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 19)
    - TDU- 2001 Convention, 2001 September; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 20)
    - Voting Breakdowns, 2001 November; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 21)
    - The Results, 2001 November; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 22)
    - Results by Craft, 2001 November; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 23)
    - Election Results, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 24)
    - EA- Access Rules, 2000 November 8; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 25)
    - Candidates Victory Statements, 2001 November; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 26)
    - Credico Fax, 2001 October 9; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 27)
    - September 11- Mailing, 2001 September 11; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 28)
    - Hoffa Mailings, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 29)
    - TDU- Barbara Harvey, 2001 May 3; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 30)
    - Leedham- Canada, 2001 May 21; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 31)
    - TDU Financial Records, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 32)
    - In These Times, 2001 August 6; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 33)
    - Local 115, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 34)
    - Maria Martinez, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 35)
    - Leedham Slate, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 36)
    - Leedham- Press, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 37)
    - Leedham Announces, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 38)
    - Local 556, 1999, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 39)
    - Leedham- UPS, 1999-2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 40)
    - Leedham Leaflets, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 41)
    - Local 2000, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 42)
    - Ashley McNeeley, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 43)
    - Local 2000, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 44)
    - Leedham Homepage, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 45)
    - Leedham- Petitions, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 46)
    - Local 174, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 91, Folder 47)
    - Leedham- Dirt, 2000 April 11; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Leedham Flyers, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Metz, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - Leedham Donations- May 2000, 2000 May; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - Morris- Leedham, 1998 February 20; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - Leedham Fundraising, 2000 May 25; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Leedham Staff, 1998-2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 7)
    - The Nation- Hoffa, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 8)
    - Labor Notes, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 9)
    - AUD, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 10)
    - 2000- TDU Convention, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 11)
    - TDU- Leedham, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 12)
    - TDU- Respect, Integrity, Strength, Ethics (RISE), 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 13)
    - Convoy- 1997, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 14)
    - Convoy- 1998, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 15)
    - Convoy- 1999, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 16)
    - Convoy- 2000, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 17)
    - Convoy- 2001, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 18)
    - TDU- Leedham, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 19)
    - TDU- Deaner, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 20)
    - TDU- Tarpinian, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 21)
    - TDU- 1996 IBT Convention, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 22)
    - AUD, 2001 February-March; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 23)
    - Labor Notes, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 24)
    - Rules- Raymond, 1999-2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 25)
    - Rules- Comments, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 92, Folder 26)
    - Election 2001, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Approved Rules, 2000 February 29; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Rules- Department of Labor (DOL), 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Rules- Judge February 2000, 2000 February; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Edelstein Approves Rules, 2000 May 4; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Judge Rejects Rules, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Election Rules, 2000 May 4; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Rules- DOL, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - TDU October Bundle Flyers, 2001 October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Hoffa Slate/Leedham Slate VHS Tape, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Original Box List for 2001 Election, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Hoffa- Local 776, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Leedham- Deaner, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Hoffa- Fundraising Guide, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 14)
    - Leebove Decision, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 15)
    - Hoffa Research- TDU, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 16)
    - Hoffa Volunteers, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 17)
    - Hoffagram, 2001 August 28; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 18)
    - Hoffa Leaflets, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 19)
    - Labor Union Delegate Elections, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 20)
    - Local 773, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 21)
    - Local 326- Endorsement, 2000 October 26; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 22)
    - Cammack Literature, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 23)
    - Hoffa Fundraisers, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 24)
    - Amendments and Resolutions, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 25)
    - Petition Fax to Locals June 2000, 2000 June; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 26)
    - John Rabine, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 27)
    - Hogan- Local 714, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 28)
    - Tom Keegel, 2000 November 20; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 29)
    - Locals by Craft, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 30)
    - Leebove- Campaign Strategy, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 31)
    - Phil Young, 2001 February; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 32)
    - Press- Hoffa, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 33)
    - 2000- Election Press, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 93, Folder 34)
    - Delegates Needed to Nominate, 2000 June 1; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Peititon Packet Given to Candidates, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - Local Delegate Elections, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - Hogan Petition, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - Hoffa Slate Petition, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - Petition Mailing June, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Hoffa Petition Plan, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Petition Faxed to Locals, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Hoffa Petition Blast Faxes, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - 1999- LM-2, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - Hoffa- Fundraisers, 2001 March 15; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - Hoffa Slate Meeting- 2001, Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - Hoffa- Donation Forms, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - Hoffa- Flyers, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - Local 705, 1999-2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - Felice- Graphics, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - Hoffa- PA, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - Teamster 'Ads', 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - Hoffa Slate Petition, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - Legal & Accounting Fundraiser, 1999-2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - Hoffa- Declaration of Support, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - Disclaimer, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - Hoffa Candidates, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 23)
    - Hoffa- Fundraisers, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - First Slate Mailing, 2000 May 3; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 25)
    - Hoffa- Magazine, 2000-2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 26)
    - EA- Advisory of Magazine 'Ads', 2000 July 21; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - Advisory on Petitions, 2000; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 28)
    - Advisory on Literature Tables, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 29)
    - Teamster Locals, 1999; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 30)
    - Seasonal Locals, 2000 May 3; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 31)
    - Advisory on Campaign Contributions & Disclosure, 2000 September 27; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 32)
    - Hoffa Unity Slate Contributions, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 33)
    - August 2001, 2001 August; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 34)
    - August 2001, 2001 August; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 35)
    - August 2001, 2001 August; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 36)
    - August 2001, 2001 August; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 94, Folder 37)
    - September 2001, 2001 September; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - September 2001, 2001 September; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - September 2001, 2001 September; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - September 2001, 2001 September; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - October 2001, 2001 October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - October 2001, 2001 October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - October 2001, 2001 October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - October 2001, 2001 October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - November 2001, 2001 November; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - November 2001, 2001 November; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - IBT Magazine, 2001; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    - Original Box List for 2001 Election, Undated; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - July 2000, 2000 July; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - August 2000, 2000 August; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - August 2000, 2000 August; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - September 2000, 2000 September; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - October 2000, 2000 October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - October 2000, 2000 October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - October 2000, 2000 October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - October 2000, 2000 October; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 9)
    - November 2000, 2000 November; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - November 2000, 2000 November; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 11)
    - December 2000, 2000 December; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 12)
    - December 2000, 2000 December; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 96, Folder 13)
    - January 2001, 2001 January; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - January 2001, 2001 January; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - January 2001, 2001 January; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - January 2001, 2001 January; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - February 2001, 2001 February; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - February 2001, 2001 February; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - February 2001, 2001 February; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - February 2001, 2001 February; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - April 2001, 2001 April; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - March 2001, 2001 March; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - March 2001, 2001 March; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - March 2001, 2001 March; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - March 2001, 2001 March; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - March 2001, 2001 March; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - April 2001, 2001 April; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - May 2001, 2001 May; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - May 2001, 2001 May; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - May 2001, 2001 May; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - June 2001, 2001 June; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - June 2001, 2001 June; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - July 2001, 2001 July; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - July 2001, 2001 July; Series 8 Subseries 4 (Box 98, Folder 12)
- Convention Files, 1986-2006; Series 9; 2 Linear Feet
  This series contains documentation on three IBT international conventions.
  Series 9 is arrangedchronologically by convention date.
  - 1986 Convention and 1999 Overnite Strike, 1986, 1999-2005; Series 9 Subseries 1; 1.5 Linear Feet
    - Original Box List for 1986 Convention and 1999 Overnite Strike, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Teamster VHS Tape, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - 23rd Convention- Agenda, 1986 May 19-23; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - 23rd- Teamster Magazine, 1986 May-June; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Canadian Conference, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Trade Divisions, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Teamster 23rd Convention Materials, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Proposed By-Law Changes, 1986 May 19; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Convention Gala, 1986 May 20 & 22; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - Delegate List, 1986 May 19; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - Theme Song, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - IBT- A Success Story, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - Trade Divisions, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - 1986- IBT Convention, 1986 May; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - 23rd- The Press, 1986 May; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - Las Vegas Press, 1986 May; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - IBT Officers Report, 1986 May 19-23; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - 23rd- Local Union Press, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - IBT and the Press, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - Trade Divisions, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - IBT Legal Department, 1986 May 19-23; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - 23rd and TDU, 1986; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - UPS= Overnite, 2005; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Overnite, 1999 July 23; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Overnite, 1999-2000, 2002; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - American Standoff, 2002; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Overnite, 1999 July 14; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Overnite, 1999; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Overnite Strike Materials, 1999-2000; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Overnite, 1999, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Overnite, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - "American Standoff" VHS Tape, 2002 June 10; Series 9 Subseries 1 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - 2001 Convention, 1996, 2000-2001; Series 9 Subseries 2; 1.5 Linear Feet
    - Original Box List for 2001 Convention, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Teamsters 26th Convention VHS Tape, 2001 June 25-29; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Committee Selections, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Committee Selections, 2000-2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Schedules, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Diversity Position, 2000 November 27; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Leedham, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Resolutions, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - News Articles, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Press Releases, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - 2001- IBT Convention, Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - 2001- IBT Convention, Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - 2001- IBT Convention, Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Leo Deaner, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - 1996- IBT Convention, Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Delegate Voting, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Teamsters National Black Caucus (TNBC), 2001 August 21-26; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Rules Committee, 2001 June 25-29; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - IBT Convention February 7 Meeting, 2000 February 7; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - US Attorney- Convention, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - IBT Agenda, 2001 June 25-29; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 21)
    - Convention Press Releases, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 22)
    - Retiree Lunch, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 23)
    - Hoffa Slate News, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 24)
    - Convention News, 2001 June 25-29; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 25)
    - Diversity Committee, 2001 June 25-29; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 26)
    - Spouses Lunch, 2001 June 27; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 27)
    - Committee Members, 2001 June 25-29; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 28)
    - Resolutions Committee, 2001 June 25-29; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 29)
    - Proposed Constitution, 2001 June 25-29; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 30)
    - 1st Day Proceedings, 2001 June 25; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - 2nd Day Proceedings, 2001 June 26; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - 3rd Day Proceedings, 2001 June 27; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - 4th Day Proceedings, 2001 June 28; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - 5th Day Proceedings, 2001 June 29; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - List of Delegates, 2001 June 25-29; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - IBT Departments, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Trade Conferences, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Trade Divisions, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - 2001- IBT Convention, Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Convention Pictures, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Convention ID, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Organizing Leaflets, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Officers Report, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Convoy Dispatch, 2001 June-July; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Constitution Committee, 2001; Series 9 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 16)
  - 2006 Convention, Series 9 Subseries 3; 1 Linear Feet
    - Original Box List for 2006 Convention, Undated; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Constitution Committee Materials, 2006 June 26-30; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Convention Black Book: Day 1, 2006 June 26; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Convention Black Book: Day 2, 2006 June 27; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Convention Black Book (Hoffa): Day 3, 2006 June 28; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Convention Black Book: Day 4, 2006 June 29; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Convention Black Book: Day 5, 2006 June 30; Series 9 Subseries 3 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Local Union Trusteeship Files, 1964-2005; Series 10; 2 Linear Feet
  This series contains documentation on IBT local unions that were put under trusteeship by the international.
  This series is arranged numerically by local union.